The host is holding a massive golden
microphone that is too heavy to carry.
People so close to me are struggling
right now and yet I'm talking about the
engineering concepts of
building 240 workflows.
I'm just scaring people off.
Last week, I made a decision.
I'm going to pivot, building tools with
no code and no technical background.
So you can become a delivery pilot and
make sure you are
transforming in the AIH.
Everybody will get their jet pack on and
they are gonna look ahead.
I'm talking with someone, a friend of
mine who escaped from the war.
Think about this like a giant glass that
she's outside and there's no code tools
for her to survive
this billion dollar war.
I'm unlikely to get this golden
microphone anyway from the engineers in
the enterprises that I work for.
They are moving like zombie snails in a
10 year race to be able to get there for
the AI transformation.
There's a massive
resistance, but we are closing the gap.
I want everybody to be able to use the
simulations, do their checklist, clone
the repos, fork them and create their
bespoke applications using the AI.
The scene, the statue
hall, the screen capture,
static rules.
A visual, a row of a frozen statues,
static versus a character
made out of liquid mercury,
changing shapes like the terminator.
It's dynamic.
The static rules are easily broken.
If you look at these rules you are going
to see that they are hard-coded, rigid
and can easily break at day
one when the things change.
dynamic rules is like liquid mercury
rather than stone statues.
This is our key in the age of AI, I
expect everybody to be able to create
their own applications.
We build these bespoke apps using
anti-gravity, using cloth so everybody
can scout their own reality.
You are not just bonded with
the schools, the old system.
We want the power that becomes our heavy
iron chain that is difficult to escape,
the school system, the things that we
learned in the past.
They are right now obsolete.
We are going to break our chains and we
will be able to build our own solutions.
The scene, the clone lab, the screen
capture, terminal git clone demo.
So getting GitHub repositories to your
local powerhouse is the key for us to be
able to run these agents.
What we are going to do it is the magic
of the delivery pilot
template is the key.
First of all, we are going to clone that
repository to an empty folder.
Once we have the clone repository, we are
going to use the agent to be able to
execute the commands.
Then we are going to have
the tooling system for us.
We are going to see we could either use a
standard tool or we could
definitely use other tools for us.
The standard tool is the free tier.
If you don't want to spend any money, you
are going to use the free tier.
The next is the tooling.
If you don't want to use any money, use
the standard kit and you will be able to
use the Visual Studio
and the GitHub for free.
This is the way to go for the starters.
Then if you want to have a pair pilot,
you can definitely use the GitHub
co-pilot to be able to do your job.
But if you want something on your local
that is going to run with the agents on
your local, then using something like a
cursor AI makes more sense.
Think about this like an evolution.
I use three of them and I will be able to
swap between each other.
The visual, a machine that is 3D printing
in an identical copy of the host.
The foundation is the
reusable delivery pilot.
I'm creating the repositories, I'm
cloning myself and you learn how to clone
yourself in the future.
By being able to learn how to clone
yourself, you are going to
move between the AI providers.
I will show you how to glue this in a
free environment and also show this how
to be able to do this with the agents.
This is like the giant floating islands.
You are going to be able to
move from one to the other.
So you are going to learn how to operate
it on your local and how to operate in an
enterprise environment
when it is time for the
and the internet kill switch.
This is the master part that we are going
to be able to deploy our website by
understanding the GitHub actions.
good part of the GitHub actions is every
change that we do, we will be able to
deploy this using a CI
CD pipeline as a web page.
And we will be able to see the live
execution type and the
live website in our system.
So we can see all of our
changes at once very easily.
We have two thousand three minutes, that
is the key for us, that we can deploy
these minutes to web pages.
If you go to an enterprise, you are going
to see that there will be self runners
happening in the
background that is going to work
Or you can go to alternatives and buy the
enterprise solutions to be able to deploy
with optimized speed.
Because this is going to be slow but
useful for you to be
able to do your changes.
You can go to the enterprise, get GitHub
co-pilot and get more minutes.
Or you can get your own bugs to be able
to do everything yourself.
So this is going to give
you much more flexibility.
But always start from the GitHub actions.
transformation.
The scene, the nursery host arrow.
A visual, a giant GitHub logo
acting as a baby's nightlight.
If you are a mom or a dad putting kids to
bed, like myself,
consistency is your magic shield.
Today, we are going to build something
that I'm using in my flat.
This workflow is a giant red
off lever for the internet.
It lives and breathes inside GitHub.
It turns the internet
on and off in the flat.
We are going to add special features,
bespoke features for us to be able to
turn only one kid's internet, turn the
other kid's internet on.
So we might start a fight,
but we know what we are doing.
We are going to give this to the mom so
the mom can do the
updates that she wants.
The screen capture, Google MSFT.
A visual, a Google and a Microsoft logo
colored head and holding an Alexa speaker
like a crystal ball.
I saw a colleague from my Microsoft days.
He mentioned, "Why don't you use a Google
skills or Alexa skills?
They will always
speak in the background."
These are the skills that you are going
to find out in your own use cases.
The delivery pilot
framework, the simulations
and the
If you try to come up with the solutions
yourself, such as using the Google Play,
you are going to see that this is going
to be a walled garden for you, which
means you are going to be locked in to
the system while you
are trying to use it.
There's all these skills that is already
designed and you are going
to have the privacy text.
You are going to share
your data to the Google.
Learning tools like Ozur is going to
bring you overhead because you have to
learn tools like Ozur and there's going
to be lots of points that you have to
learn to be able to run it and it might
not be very straight forward
in your home lab environment.
And you are going to go through all these
constraints and the
costs and the friction
of your waste.
You are going to see that there is lots
of hardware that's going to get not used
and you want to have a privacy and you
want to be able to use something that you
own instead of you are renting it from
somebody else and you are going to have
an infinite control on the
structure that you created.
delivery structure is
for you to figure out.
I'm creating the structure.
I'm showing you how I am doing it.
Your responsibility is take the delivery
pilot and go wherever you wanna go.
The scene, the engine room,
the host aero, the visual.
Host is standing in front of a clock
where the hands are
spinning at 1000X speed.
We are triggering an AI transformation or
hands-on experience by building our own
solutions using the
artificial intelligence.
We are in an ever
spinning engine of learning.
I started with the books.
I read the basic.
Right now we have the
smartest operators in the room.
All the books, all the videos are inside
the AI agents waiting for you to be able
to be turn your
creativity into something gold.
The scene, the kitchen table, the screen
capture and the home network dashboard.
The AI learning frontier, we are going to
use all these large language models to
knowledge acquisition.
We are going to use the quote "Capture,
organize, distill and express framework"
and all the data will come as a capture
for you while we are learning.
So, you are going to see Claude solves
most of the problems.
Then there is the chat GPT.
You can easily say why chat GPT is not
the first because Claude's models are
very very focused on it.
Then my favorite, the
free one, the deep seek.
Any time that you need a large language
model you know that it is there and it
has lots of potential and if you want
something versatile like the Gemini that
you can use nano banana to create images
you can do slides plus you can do the
code as well on the Gemini
and it is a big free tier as
Why the Claude is good?
Why we need to use the Claude?
Because the reasoning layer is top notch
with the Sonnet 3.5, right now 4.5 and
4.6 we see that it is able to solve the
most complex problems.
As we mentioned chat GPT is versatile.
It is the leading tool in the AI space.
We will be able to use it.
I mostly use it as a search engine for
myself and you can do
this by a Chrome extension.
The deep seek is the coding disruptor.
You are going to see that this free
structure that is going to help you a lot
and you should be able to copy paste this
code outside of the editors which you
want to use it for free.
The last but not the least the Gemini is
the versatile platform which integrates
with all these tools and you will be able
to see the Google does not want to lose
the search it will give you images.
It is going to give you videos.
It is going to give you a coding editor
for them to be able to
keep the search business.
For you to be able to master the code in
seconds what you need to do it is you
need to be able to explain yourself in
English very very easily.
Understand the AI is generating it and
you need to learn how to debug this
yourself to be able to get better at
So let's talk about the free tier.
All of these free tiers have a use case.
I start with the chat GPT when it gets
finished I will go to deep seek.
If that doesn't work I will go to Gemini
and if I can't really solve something I
might need to pay money for the cloud if
my free subscription is ending.
Also don't forget all of these have
different skills and we are going to see
with those different skills coding
reasoning creativity and ecosystem there
are different use cases for different
types of large language models.
So what you need to do it is you need to
make sure you focus on learning and you
set a path for yourself by using all
these tools go to their website plus also
use their mobile app
A visual, a kitchen table flowing with
100 tablets like a
digital food getting served.
It's a feast.
Why not turn YouTube into a hobby?
This is a family oriented week.
Instead of serving food,
today we are serving tablets.
We are building these interfaces for our
use cases to manage the access in our
household, in your flat.
So think of this as a digital gatekeeper
and you are going to build it using
cloth, using Gemini, using DeepSeek.
You are going to be the one who is going
to be in charge and you are going to have
this pure creativity on your side.
The scene, the power
station, the power screen capture.
We have the router table.
A visual, a lightning bolt being caught
in a small glass bottle.
If I flip the switch and track the
lighting, I lose the
target light instantly.
So join me, learn the flow
with the speed of the waterfall
and the clarity of the diamond.
This is your key moment.
You are going to see that you will be
able to capture everything that you do if
you get your hands on and turn this on.
The scene, the tool shed screen, the
capture, the GitHub and the tool demo.
Visual, all visual toolbox where the
tools are literally
vibrating with energy.
Let's look at what I'm doing with the
Internet Access Manager.
I'm trying to create it with my delivery
pilot framework, so I can have a
framework on top of the system that I'm
going to build, because this is going to
be a bespoke solution for myself.
If we look down to this, we are going to
see that this is generated in an 8N, and
I have all these different types of
triggers to be able to turn on the
Internet and turn off the Internet, and I
have a logic that follows up and sends a
telegram message and then email at the
end, so I know that the Internet is on.
This is my logic, this is
my bespoke implementation.
This is working behind my own system in
the background where I ran
an edge router in the back.
Everybody will have a different router,
so they are going to
program this in a different way.
main thing that I'm doing is I have the
MAC addresses, and I'm going to add a
drop rule on here to be able to drop the
traffic that I don't want
on here very, very easily.
But you are going to realize I have all
the MAC addresses mapped to all of the
devices in the flat, so it is very
straightforward for me to be able to
start or stop a
device getting the access.
I have also created a user interface that
I mentioned on GitHub using the GitHub
Pages feature and deploying this on here,
which one of the features is adding
turning the Internet on, turning the
Internet off, looking at the device list,
because this is going to have the
firewall policies, and I have all the
implementation guide for myself.
And this is for my wife to be able to use
it, because I do not want to give my wife
a complex solution where she has got
issues turning on and
turning off the Internet.
Because this is an agentic system, as we
see on here, we are going to see that
most of the time this works automatically
in the background, and new rules are
coming up all the time.
So the rules are dynamic,
I can always extend them.
Because this is an agentic system as we
see on here, we are going to see that
most of the time this works automatically
in the background and new rules are
coming up all the time.
So the rules are
dynamic, I can always extend
There's two critical
places that I can look.
First of all, I can go to my commits in
the GitHub repository, which is private,
and see how many
times I change the system.
As we see on here, this has been changed
more than 37 times, and I have different
rules coming up on different times.
As I said, this is going
to evolve all the time.
This is a bespoke solution.
I will always change, update, and remove
the existing features.
While I'm adding new features, I will be
able to see all my executions, and when
did it work, and when did it
not work very, very easily.
As I have seen on
here, something happened.
I have updated the code base.
For the last couple of
days, it is not working.
Normally, it was working.
I should be able to go down into this
system, and be able to see that it was
working in the past very easily.
I should be able to scroll down and see
this was working on here.
I deployed something
and broke the system down.
So I will be able to see how many times
this has worked in the past, and what did
I need to do to be able to
make this work easier for myself.
There are all these different use cases
on here that I can add
definitely onto the system.
This is going to make my life much easier
to be able to manage this system, such as
I added a device control on here to be
able to turn on and
off a specific device.
That's a new feature that I'm trying to
add, but I have broken
other parts of the system.
I need to make sure I'm always looking at
it and learning through this process.
The main thing that you can do, I have
shared this in other videos, you can
definitely come into here and set an
error workflow to make sure that if one
of your workflows is failing, you will be
able to get a direct message.
Here is my niche update.
I'm using the memory palaces.
Let's transform all together.
Grab your hammer.
That is the gate that is
vibrating and your compass.
It could be your programmable router.
In my case, it is.
I'm using the NA10.
I'm using my compute.
In your case, it could be your laptop.
Find the things that is your own
environment in the
delivery pilot structure.
Build your bespoke solutions.
Apps, what you love.
Do what you wanna do.
Focus on learning.
Focus on self-learning for
yourself, for your family.
Let's look at the tool shed, a complete
GitHub Toolbox for modern developers.
The repository anatomy, mastering the
structure of the professional base.
Once I do the delivery pilot, I always
start with the reel
and end with the testing.
And there's all these
stages come in the middle.
The structure to have an organized system
is important to create a modular system
where you can track your assets and you
can separate your configuration and be
able to do an X times N, meaning loss of
repositories with the
least amount of effort.
While you are going to work on the
repost, the main thing that you are going
to get through is your ability to be able
to write everything in a readme file.
So this is the markdown format and you
are going to have always an operational
procedure for yourself how to use the
repository in a hierarchical manner so
you can read and then
study your environment.
issues tab and the pull requests are the
critical parts on GitHub where you are
going to work on one project, you are
going to see there is lots of issues
coming up and things that are changing
and you have to be able to merge your
branches to make sure that you have one
trunk that is always green and make sure
that you are always doing
the continuous integration.
The collaboration
function is the fork mechanism.
Once you fork a repository what is
happening is you are getting all the code
pieces and you see all the
history coming up in the project.
You will be upstream syncing and you will
be able to open to contributions.
You are going to create your
own version of the program.
If you look at the development cycle, you
first clone the repo, you start
customizing it, then you want to get
certified, you want to be able to deploy,
you want to be able to
create your own program.
Let's look at what is free.
The GitHub part is completely free.
Downloading Visual Studio is free, having
a git repository is free and if you want
to run environments, different programs,
the docker is free for you.
The main start is you
start always with zero capital.
Once you start with zero capital, you
don't have monthly investment on the
system, you are mostly putting the money
into your journey
which you need to focus on.
If we compare the free versions, you get
all the Visual Studio plugins.
Once you go to paid IDs such as the
JetBrains or use a GitHub co-pilot, you
are going to spend more
money to be able to do more.
So these are going to come in once you
want to do more of the stuff and you want
to have dedicated timelines on here and
advanced security features.
But having private repos and being able
to build this on GitHub is always free.
The scene, the balcony, the host arrow.
Host looking out over the futuristic city
being built by the
drones using the simulations.
Every simulation
starts with the assessment.
Make sure that you take the assessment
first, then go and watch
the simulations video second.
Once you launch the assessment, you are
going to see all your skills gaps at
start, so you need to understand where
you are gapping the issues.
You watch the video on the top and at the
bottom there's a checklist.
Make sure that you are checking network
authentication profile resources.
With every video you are going to get a
different checklist.
So this is vital for you to make sure
that you are able to sync
up with what is in the video.
Once you complete your simulation
running, meaning you are going to have a
program that runs in the background, that
is the clone of this
application that you can turn it on.
This is the vital stage
for you to be able to turn
Once you are able to do this, you are
going to see that you will run this in
different amounts on Windows, iOS,
Android, on code spaces.
Different environments
is very, very important.
And you are going to soon realize this is
not only one device that you are going to
run, you are going to run a mesh of
devices and they are going to get
connected to each other.
The dashboards are very critical.
I always encourage you to be able to
deploy a website and make sure that you
are doing it with the GitHub actions and
iterate on this all the time.
So this is going to give you the real
feeling of what you really need to
Such as in my case, the kids devices and
I'm responding to their controls and this
process is always going to change because
I have kids, they are at
three years old to nine years old.
The use cases for three years old is very
different than the use
cases in nine year old.
So I need to make sure I play the game by
their rules and understand what are my
requirements and what are my changes.
Looking at the logs, the event streams on
the GitHub or the NA10 is very critical
for you to understand the automatic
triggers and the audit trail is very,
very important because at the end of
today, you want to have a secure
environment doing this and working like a
clock for you is very, very critical.
What will be your success metrics?
You want to make sure that you are
compliant, you have lots of accuracy.
In the beginning, you
might not start very current.
In the beginning, you might have more
latency because you are using free tools.
And at the end of today, you want to have
make sure you are learning through this
process, which is the
key for your self growth.
Building your own, that is
the maximum that you can go.
To become a delivery pilot, what we want
you is, we want you to be able to come
out of this simulation and
build your own local environment.
So we start with cloning the repo first,
then starting configuring.
Make sure after you configure, you create
your own environment.
I have built these simulations for you.
Build the future with me.
Till next time.
Love.
Bye-bye, bye-bye.